Finding Aid for Michael T. Alexander papers, 1968-1994
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Systems Reports 1968-1991
  - Usage Statistics, Public Files and Print Jobs 1977-1988 (Box 7)
  - Usage Statistics, U-Blue System 1982-1990, 4 folders (Box 7)
- Vendors 1973-1987
  The Vendors series includes proposals for the purchase of IBM and Amdahl mainframe computers as well as records documenting the long-standing relationship between the UM Computing Center and Amdahl Corporation during the 1970s and 1980s.
  - Amdahl Corporation, Early Correspondence 1973-1987, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Proposal to Purchase Amdahl 580 1981 (Box 7)
  - Proposal to Purchase IBM 3081 Processor Complex, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Proposal to Purchase NAS AS/9000DPC 1981 (Box 7)
Related Material
Material at the Bentley Historical Library related to the Michael T. Alexander papers include the following:
Units and departments:
Computing Center records
Computing Center publications
Information Technology Division records
Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research records
Logic of Computers Group records
Merit Network, Inc. records
University Committee on Computer Policy and Utilization records
Individuals associated with the Computing Center and its work:
Arthur W. Burks papers
Bernard Galler papers
Aaron Finerman papers
The HathiTrust Digital Library (http://hathitrust.org) also contains various publications and papers by or about the U-M Computing Center. These materials have been collected into a
UM Computing Center Collection
Michigan Terminal System Archive
: http://archive.michigan-terminal-system.org/home (Accessed on February 3, 2012.)
MTS page on Wikipedia
: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michigan_Terminal_System (Accessed 2012.)